{
    "HCI": {
        "Chapter_1": {
            "Definition_of_HCI": {
                "answers": ["Human-Computer Interaction","Cognitive Science","Computer Science", "Interaction", "Information Science", "Pshychology"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "It the study of the interaction between people and computers.",
                        "answer": ["Human-Computer Interaction","HCI","Human Computer Interaction"],
                        "id": 1
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is is a multidisciplinary field that draws knowledge and methods from various discipline to understand and improve the interaction between humans and computers.",
                        "answer": ["Human-Computer Interaction","HCI","Human Computer Interaction"],
                        "id": 2
                    }
                    
                ],
                
                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Human", "Humans"], ["Computer", "Computers"], ["Interaction", "Interactions"]],
                    "question": "Fundamental Components of HCI",
                    "id": 3
                }
            },

            "History_of_HCI": {
                "answers": ["Memex system", "Mouse", "Sketchpad", "Alto computer", "Macintosh computer", "World Wide Web", "iPhone", "Google glass"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "(1945)Vennevar Bush describes a ________, which is a precursor to hypertext.",
                        "answer": ["Memex system"],
                        "id": 4
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(1962)Douglas Engelbert introduces this concept ________.",
                        "answer": ["Mouse","The first mouse"],
                        "id": 5
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(1968)Ivan Sutherland develops ________, one of the first graphical user interfaces.",
                        "answer": ["Sketchpad"],
                        "id": 6
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(1973)Xerox PARC develops the ________, which features a graphical user interface similar to the Macintosh.",
                        "answer": ["Alto computer"],
                        "id": 7
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(1984)The ________ is released, popularizing the use of graphical user interfaces.",
                        "answer": ["Macintosh computer"],
                        "id": 8
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(1993)The ________ is created, which makes it possible for people to interact with computer over the internet.",
                        "answer": ["World Wide Web","WWW"],
                        "id": 9
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(2007)The ________ was released, which popularized the use of touchscreens.",
                        "answer": ["iPhone","iphone","Iphone"],
                        "id": 10
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(2011)The first commercial augmented reality(AR) headset was ________.",
                        "answer": ["Google glass"],
                        "id": 11
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [ ["Memex system"], ["Mouse"], ["Sketchpad"], ["Alto computer"], ["Macintosh computer"], ["World Wide Web"], ["iPhone"], ["Google glass"]],
                    "question": "Concepts in History of HCI",
                    "id": 12
                }
            },

            "Primary_Goal_of_HCI": {
                "answers": ["Usability", "User Experience", "Accessibility", "Safety and Reliability", "Efficiency and Performance", "Adaptability and Flexibility", "Ethical and Social Considerations"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the ease with which a user can interact with a system or product to achieve their goals. A system or product is considered usable if it is intuitive, efficient, and user-friendly.",
                        "answer": ["Usability", "Usabilities"],
                        "id": 13
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Encompasses the overall feelings, perceptions, and responses of a user when interacting with a product or system. It includes aspects like satisfaction, enjoyment, efficiency, and effectiveness of the interaction.",
                        "answer": ["User Experience", "User Experiences"],
                        "id": 14
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Concerned with making technology and digital content usable by individuals with disabilities. This includes ensuring that people with various impairments can perceive, understand, navigate, and interact with digital systems.",
                        "answer": ["Accessibility", "Accessibilities"],
                        "id": 15
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Ensuring that a system or product is free from errors, crashes, and security vulnerabilities. Users should feel confident that the technology will perform as expected without harming them or their data.",
                        "answer": ["Safety and Reliability"],
                        "id": 16
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the system's ability to accomplish tasks quickly and with minimal effort on the part of the user. It involves how well a system or product performs its intended functions.",
                        "answer": ["Efficiency and Performance", "Efficiency and Performances"],
                        "id": 17
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refer to a system's ability to adapt to different user needs or changing circumstances. An adaptable and flexible system can be customized to suit different user preferences and requirements.",
                        "answer": ["Adaptability and Flexibility", "Adaptabilities and Flexibilities"],
                        "id": 18
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "They involve addressing the ethical implications of technology use and its impact on society. This includes issues like data privacy, security, bias, and the broader societal implications of technology.",
                        "answer": ["Ethical and Social Considerations", "Ethical and Social Consideration", "Ethical and Socials Considerations", "Ethical and Socials Consideration"],
                        "id": 19
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Usability"], ["User Experience"], ["Accessibility"], ["Safety and Reliability", "Safety and Reliabilities"], ["Efficiency and Performance", "Efficiency and Performances"], ["Adaptability and Flexibility"], ["Ethical and Social Considerations", "Ethical and Social Consideration"]],
                    "question": "Enumerate the Primary Goal of HCI",
                    "id": 20
                }
            },

            "Disciplines_Contributing_to_HCI": {
                "answers": ["Psychology", "Computer Science", "Design", "Human Factors and Ergonomics", "Cognitive Science", "Information Science", "Anthropology and Sociology", "Linguistics", "Ethnography"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Involves the study of human behavior, cognition, and emotions as they relate to the use of technology. Psychologists in HCI research areas like user behavior, perception, decision-making, and user motivation to inform design and user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Psychology"],
                        "id": 21
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Provides the technical foundation for HCI. It encompasses the development of software, hardware, and systems that facilitate human-computer interaction. Computer scientists in HCI work on creating technology that is efficient, functional, and user-friendly.",
                        "answer": ["Computer Science"],
                        "id": 22
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the process of creating user interfaces and overall user experiences. Designers focus on the visual and interaction aspects of software and hardware to ensure that they are aesthetically pleasing and easy to use.",
                        "answer": ["Design"],
                        "id": 23
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This field focuses on designing technology to fit human capabilities, limitations, and comforts.",
                        "answer": ["Human Factors and Ergonomics","Human Factor and Ergonomics","Human Factors and Ergonomic"],
                        "id": 24
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Concerned with the study of human cognition, including memory, attention, problem-solving, and decision-making. HCI researchers draw from cognitive science to understand how users process information and make decisions when interacting with technology.",
                        "answer": ["Cognitive Science"],
                        "id": 25
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Involves the management and organization of information, data, and knowledge. In HCI, it's important for designing systems that present information in a structured and understandable manner.",
                        "answer": ["Information Science"],
                        "id": 26
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Brings a cultural and social perspective to HCI. Researchers in these fields study how technology is adopted and used in different cultural and social contexts, considering factors like values, norms, and societal impact.",
                        "answer": ["Anthropology and Sociology"],
                        "id": 27
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Understanding how language and communication play a role in user interfaces, voice recognition, and natural language processing. It helps in designing interfaces that effectively interpret and generate human language.",
                        "answer": ["Linguistics","Linguistic"],
                        "id": 28
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is a research method used in HCI to observe and understand how people use technology in their natural environments. It involves immersive field studies to gain insights into user behaviors, needs, and contexts.",
                        "answer": ["Ethnography"],
                        "id": 29
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Psychology"], ["Computer Science"], ["Design"], ["Human Factors and Ergonomics", "Human Factor and Ergonomic", "Human Factors and Ergonomic", "Human Factor and Ergonomics"], ["Cognitive Science"], ["Information Science"], ["Anthropology and Sociology"], ["Linguistics", "Linguistic"], ["Ethnography"]],
                    "question": "Enumerate the Disciplines Contributing to HCI",
                    "id": 30
                }
            },

            "Importance_of_HCI": {
                "answers": ["User-Friendly Design", "Avoiding Errors and Frustration", "Real-World Application", "Integration with the Design Process", "Legal and safety requirements"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Involves creating interfaces and systems that are intuitive, easy to use, and enjoyable for users. It focuses on designing with the user's needs and preferences in mind, minimizing the learning curve, and providing a positive user experience.",
                        "answer": ["User-Friendly Design","User Friendly Design"],
                        "id": 31
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It involves designing interfaces that prevent users from making mistakes, providing clear feedback, and guiding users to achieve their goals without undue frustration.",
                        "answer": ["Avoiding Errors and Frustration","Avoiding Error and Frustration","Avoiding Errors and Frustrations","Avoiding Error and Frustrations"],
                        "id": 32
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to designing computer systems and interfaces that align with the way users naturally work and interact in their everyday lives. It aims to make technology relevant and practical, ensuring that users can easily integrate it into their existing routines and tasks.",
                        "answer": ["Real-World Application","Real World Application"],
                        "id": 33
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Integrating HCI considerations into the design process means involving HCI experts and usability testing throughout the development cycle. This ensures that usability and user experience factors are considered from the initial design stages and continue to be addressed throughout the development process.",
                        "answer": ["Integration with the Design Process","Integration with Design Process"],
                        "id": 34
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Dealing with sensitive data or applications that may pose risks to users. It involves adhering to regulations, standards, and guidelines to protect user data, ensure product safety, and meet legal obligations in various domains.",
                        "answer": ["Legal and Safety Requirements","Legal and Safety Requirement","Legals and Safety Requirements","Legals and Safety Requirement"],
                        "id": 35
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["User-Friendly Design", "User Friendly Design", "User-Friendly Designs", "User Friendly Designs"], ["Avoiding Errors and Frustration", "Avoiding Errors and Frustrations", "Avoiding Error and Frustrations", "Avoiding Error and Frustration"], ["Real-World Application", "Real World Application", "Real-World Applications", "Real World Applications"], ["Integration with the Design Process", "Integration with the Designs Process"], ["Legal and safety requirements"]],
                    "question": "Enumerate the Importance of HCI",
                    "id": 36
                }
            }
        },

        "Chapter_2.1": {
            "The_Human_Component_of_HCI": {
                "answers": ["Human", "Model Human Processor", "Sensory Memories", "Attention", "Short-term memory", "Rehearsal", "Long-term memory", "Sensory memories", "Rehearsal", "Forgetting", "Information Retrieval", "Storing information", "Episodic Memory", "Semantic Memory"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The one whom computer system are designed to assist. THe Requirements of the user should therefore be our first priority.",
                        "answer": ["Human","Humans","The Human","The Humans"],
                        "id": 165
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is a model of human information processing.",
                        "answer": ["Model Human Processor","Model Human Processor (MHP)","Model Human Processor(MHP)","MHP"],
                        "id": 166
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "A type of memory that stores information from the senses for a very short period of time.",
                        "answer": ["Sensory Memories","Sensory Memory"],
                        "id": 167
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Information from sensory memory is transferred to short-term memory through.",
                        "answer": ["Attention","Attentions"],
                        "id": 168
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is a temporary storage system that holds information that is currently being used.",
                        "answer": ["Short-term memory","Short term memory","Short term memories","Short-term memories","Short-terms memory","Short-terms memories"],
                        "id": 169
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Information from short-term memory can be transfered to long-term memory through.",
                        "answer": ["Rehearsal","Rehearsals"],
                        "id": 170
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It the part of the memory that stores information for a long period of time.",
                        "answer": ["Long-term memory","Long-term memories","Long term memory","Long term memories","Long-term memory","Long-terms memory"],
                        "id": 171
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The first step of how our memory stores information.",
                        "answer": ["Sensory memories","Sensory memory"],
                        "id": 172
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "When you give an attention into information, that information will now store in to.",
                        "answer": ["Short-term memory","Short term memory","Short-term memories","Short term memories"],
                        "id": 173
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "We need this so we can store this information in to long-term memory",
                        "answer": ["Rehearsal","Rehearsals"],
                        "id": 174
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is the inability to acces information from our memory.",
                        "answer": ["Forgetting information","Forgetting informations","Forgetting","Forgettings"],
                        "id": 175
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is what we called when we accessing information from our memory.",
                        "answer": ["Information Retrieval","Informations Retrieval","Retrieval","Retrievals"],
                        "id": 176
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "You are storing or putting information to your memory.",
                        "answer": ["Storing","Storing","Storings"],
                        "id": 177
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the system responsible for encoding, storing, and retrieving personal experiences and specific events or episodes in your life.",
                        "answer": ["Episodic Memory","Episodic Memories"],
                        "id": 178
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": " It involves the storage of factual knowledge, concepts, and information that are not tied to specific personal experiences. This type of memory encompasses a wide range of information, such as facts, concepts, language, and general knowledge about the world.",
                        "answer": ["Semantic Memory","Semantic Memories"],
                        "id": 179
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Also known as Working Memory.",
                        "answer": ["Short-term memory","Short-term memories","Short term memory","Short term memories"],
                        "id": 180
                    }  
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Visual", "Visuals"], ["Auditory", "Auditories"], ["Haptic", "Haptics"], ["Kenisthetic", "Kenisthetics"], ["Olfactory", "Olfactories"], ["Gustatory", "Gustatories"]],
                    "question": "Input Chanels",
                    "id": 181
                }
            },

            "Information_Processing": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Input-Output", "Input Output"], ["Memory"], ["Processing"]],
                    "question": "The three main components of the user as an information processing system.",
                    "id": 182
                }
            },

            "Input_-_Output_Chanel": {
                "answers": ["Visual", "Auditory", "Haptic", "Kinesthetic", "Olfactory", "Gustatory"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Head (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Visual","Visuals"],
                        "id": 211
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Eyes (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Auditory"],
                        "id": 212
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Facial Muscles (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Haptic","Haptics"],
                        "id": 213
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Vocal Apparatus (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Kinesthetic","Kinesthetics"],
                        "id": 214
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Hands and Fingers (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Olfactory","Olfactories"],
                        "id": 215
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Feet and Legs (Output to Input)",
                        "answer": ["Gustatory","Gustatories"],
                        "id": 216
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            },

            "MHP_Subsystems": {
                "answers": ["Cognitive system", "Perceptual system", "Motor system"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "This component represents how humans gather information from the environment. It involves sensory processes such as vision, hearing, touch, and other senses.",
                        "answer": ["Perceptual system", "Perceptual"],
                        "id": 198
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "It is responsible for executing physical actions in response to the information processed by the cognitive system.",
                        "answer": ["Motor system", "Motor"],
                        "id": 199
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "It is responsible for tasks such as memory, attention, problem-solving, decision-making, and language processing. It processes the information received from the perceptual system and generates actions based on that information.",
                        "answer": ["Cognitive system", "Cognitive"],
                        "id": 200
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Perceptual system", "Perceptual"], ["Motor system", "Motor"], ["Cognitive system", "Cognitive"]],
                    "question": "MHP Subsystems",
                    "id": 183
                }
            },

            "Type_of_Sensory_Momory": {
                "answers": ["Iconic memory", "Haptic Memory", "Echoic Memory"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "refers to the sensory memory associated with visual information. It is extremely short-lived, lasting only for a fraction of a second (typically less than a second).",
                        "answer": ["Iconic memory", "Iconic", "Iconic memories"],
                        "id": 185
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "the sensory memory associated with auditory information, such as sounds and spoken language. It lasts longer than iconic memory, typically around 2 to 4 seconds",
                        "answer":["Echoic Memory", "Echoic", "Echoic Memories"],
                        "id": 186
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "This sensory information helps you recognize objects, navigate your environment, and perform various tactile tasks.",
                        "answer": ["Haptic Memory", "Haptic", "Haptic Memories"],
                        "id": 187
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Iconic Memory", "Iconic", "Iconic Memories"], ["Echoic Memory", "Echoic", "Echoic Memories"], ["Haptic Memory", "Haptic", "Haptic Memories"]],
                    "question": "Type of Sensory Memory",
                    "id": 184
                }
            },

            "Processing": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [

                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Reassoning"], ["Probelem Solving", "Probelems Solving", "Probelem Solvings", "Probelems Solvings"], 
                                ["Skill Acquisition", "Skill Acquisitions", "Skills Acquisition", "Skills Acquisitions"], ["Error", "Errors"]],
                    "question": "Enumerate Processing",
                    "id": 188
                }
            },

            "Type_of_Reasoning": {
                "answers": ["Duductive Reasoning", "Inductive Reasoning", "Abductive Reasoning"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Using knowledge to draw conclusion or infer new information.",
                        "answer": ["Reasoning","Reasinings"],
                        "id": 189
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Derives a logically necessary conclusion from given premises, even if it doesn't always align with our notion of truth.",
                        "answer": ["Deductive Reasoning","Deductive"],
                        "id": 190
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Generalized from observed cases to infer information about unobserved cases, although it may not be entirely reilable.",
                        "answer": ["Inductive Resoning","Inductive"],
                        "id": 191
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Reasons from a fact to the cause of the fact, helping us derive explanations for observed events.",
                        "answer": ["Abductive Reasoning","Abductive Reasoning","Abductive"],
                        "id": 192
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Duductive"], ["inductive"], ["Abductive"]],
                    "question": "Type of Reasoning",
                    "id": 193
                }
            },

            "Problem-Solving_theories": {
                "answers": ["Problem-solving", "Gestalt theory", "Problem space theory"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "It is process of finding a solution to an unfamiliar task using the knowledge we have.",
                        "answer": ["Problem-solving","Problem solving","Problems-solving","Problems solving"],
                        "id": 194
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "In this theory, you are deviding or restructuring the problem and gaining insight to find innovattive solutions.",
                        "answer": ["Gestalt theory", "Gestalt theories"],
                        "id": 195
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "We called it a trial and error theory.",
                        "answer": ["Problem space theory", "Problems space theory"],
                        "id": 196
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Gestalt theory", "Gestalt theories"], ["Problem space theory", "Problems space theory"]],
                    "question": "Problem-Solving theories",
                    "id": 197
                }
            },

            "Skill_Acquisition": {
                "answers": ["Skill acquisition", "Transfer", "Practice", "Feedback", "Theory", "Metacognition"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the process of gaining experties and proficiency in a particular domain over time. It is a complex process that involves a number of factors.",
                        "answer": ["Skill acquisition", "Skills acquisitions", "Skill acquisitions", "Skills acquisition"],
                        "id": 202
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "It is a factor in skill acquisition that said, you are gaining skill through teaching",
                        "answer": ["Transfer", "Transfers"],
                        "id": 203
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the repetitive and purposeful engagement in a specific task or activity to improve one's skills and proficiency. In HCI, this can involve practicing user interface design, interaction techniques, or other aspects of human-computer interaction.",
                        "answer": ["Practice","Practices"],
                        "id": 204
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "involves receiving information about the quality and effectiveness of one's actions or interactions with a computer system. This information can be in the form of user testing results, usability evaluations, or direct user feedback.",
                        "answer": ["Feedback","Feedbacks"],
                        "id": 205
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the theoretical understanding and knowledge of principles, concepts, and models that underlie HCI. This knowledge can include human cognition, user experience (UX) design principles, information architecture, and various HCI models.",
                        "answer": ["Theory"],
                        "id": 206
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the awareness and understanding of one's cognitive processes, including the ability to monitor, control, and optimize one's learning and problem-solving strategies.",
                        "answer": ["Metacognition","Metacognitions"],
                        "id": 207
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Practice", "Practices"], ["Feedback", "Feedbacks"], ["Theory", "Theories"], ["Transfer", "Transfers"], ["Metacognition", "Metacognitions"]],
                    "question": "Factors in skill acquisition",
                    "id": 201
                }
            },

            "Errors": {
                "answers": ["Errors", "Mistake", "Slips"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Are unintentional actions that devirate from the desired outcome. They can range from minor inconveniences to serious consequences.",
                        "answer": ["Errors", "Error"],
                        "id": 209
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Slips", "Slip"], ["Mistakes", "Mistake"]],
                    "question": "Main type of Errors",
                    "id": 208
                }
            }
        },

        "Chapter_2.2": {  
            "Text_Entry_Devices": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["QWERTY Keyboard", "QWERTY"],[ "AZERTY Keyboard", "AZERTY"], ["DVORAK Keyboard", "DVORAK"], ["Split design keyboard"], ["Microwriter"], ["Mobile phone keypad", "Mobilephone keypad", "Mobile phone keypads"], ["Typical Key Mapping"], ["Handwriting recognition", "Handwriting recognitions"], ["Speach recognition","Speach recognitions"]],
                    "question": "Text Entry Devices",
                    "id": 75
                }
            },

            "Positioning,_Pointing,_and_Drawing": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["First Mouse", "The First Mouse"], ["Modern Mouse", "The Modern Mouse"], ["Laptop touchpad", "Laptop touchpads"], ["Trackball", "Trackball"], ["Thumbwheel", "Thumbwheels"], ["Joystick", "The Joystick"], ["Keyboard nipple"], ["Touchscreen", "Touchscreens"], ["Stylus light pen", "Stylus pen", "Stylus"], ["Traditional light pen"], ["Digitizing tablet", "Digitizing tablets"], ["Eyegaze"], ["Cursor keys and discrete positioning", "Cursor key and discrete positionings", "Cursor keys and discrete positionings", "Cursors keys and discrete positioning"]],
                    "question": "Positioning, Pointing, and Drawing",
                    "id": 76
                }
            },

            "Display_Devices": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Bitmap displays", "Bitmap display"], ["Cathode Ray Tube"], ["Liquid Crytal Display", "Liquid Crytal Displays"], ["The Gas Plasma Display", "The Gas Plasma Displays"], ["Vector Display", "Vector Displays"], ["Projector and projector screen", "Projectors and projectors screens", "Projectors and projectors screen", "Projectors and projector screens", "Projector and projector screens"], ["Concert Stage LED Screens", "Concert Stage LED Screen",  "Concert Stage LED Screens"], ["Digital paper", "Digital papers"]],
                    "question": "Display Devices",
                    "id": 77
                }
            },

            "Devices_for_VR_and_3D_Interaction": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Cockpit and virtual controls", "Cockpit and virtual control"], ["3D mouse"], ["Dataglove", "Datagloves"], ["Virtual Reality helmets", "Virtual Reality helmet"], ["Whole-body tracking", "Whole body tracking"], ["Stereoscopic Vision", "Stereoscopic Visions"], ["Small screens fitted to a pair of goggles"], ["Special spectacles with polarized lenses"], ["Hologaphic 3D Display", "Hologaphics 3D Displays", "Hologaphic 3D Displays"], ["Large flight simulators", "Large flight simulator", "Large flights simulators", "Large flights simulator"], ["Motorbike or skiing simulators", "Motorbike or skiing simulator", "Motorbikes or skiing simulators"], ["General purpose rooms called caves", "General purpose rooms called cave"]],
                    "question": "Devices for VR and 3D Interaction",
                    "id": 78
                }
            },

            "Physical_Controls,_Sensors,_and_Special_Devices": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Light-emitting diodes", "Light-emitting diode", "Light emitting diodes"], ["Gauges and dials", "Gauge and dials", "Gauge and dial"], ["Head-up Display", "Head-up Displays", "Head up Displays", "Head-ups Display"], ["Keyboards", "Keyboard"], ["Telephone Keypads", "Telephone Keypad", "Telephones Keypads"], ["Doorbell", "Doorbell"], ["Haptic Devices", "Haptics Devices", "Haptics Device"], ["Texture analysis Technology"], ["Arcades Games that generate smells"], ["Automatic Door", "Automatic Doors"], ["Energy saving lights"], ["Security Tags", "Security Tag"], ["Ultrasound", "Ultrasounds"], ["GPS"], ["Pressure sensors", "Pressure sensor"], ["Body temperature sensor", "Body temperature sensors", "Body temperatures sensors", "Body temperatures sensor"], ["Unconscious Reaction Sensor", "Unconscious Reaction Sensors", "Unconscious Reactions Sensor", "Unconscious Reactions Sensors"]],
                    "question": "Physical Controls, Sensors, and Special Devices",
                    "id": 79
                }
            },

            "Paper:_Printing_and_Scanning": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Types of dot-based printers", "Types of dot based printer", "Types of dot based printers"], ["Types of fonts", "Types of font"], ["WYSIWYG"], ["Desktop Publishing", "Desktops Publishing"], ["Document storage and retrieval systems", "Document storage and retrieval system"], ["Optical character recognition", "Optical character recognitions"], ["Electronic publishing", "Electronics publishing"]],
                    "question": "Paper: Printing and Scanning",
                    "id": 80
                }
            },

            "Memory": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["RAM and short-term memory"], ["Magnetic Disks", "Magnetic Disk"], ["Optical Disks", "Optical Disk"], ["Compression"], ["ASCII"], ["UNICODE standard", "UNICODE standards"], ["Rich text format", "Rich text formats"], ["ISO standards", "ISO standard"], ["Standard database access"]],
                    "question": "Memory",
                    "id": 81
                }
            },

            "Networks": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Networked computing"]],
                    "question": "Networked",
                    "id": 82
                }
            }
        },

        "Chapter_2.3": {
            "Interaction": {
                "answers": ["Interaction", "Responding", "Exploring", "Manipulating", "Conversing", "Instructing"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the dynamic exchange of information and actions between a user and a computer or digital system.",
                        "answer": ["Interaction", "Interactions"],
                        "id": 218
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Users provide explicit commands or instructions to a computer system to perform specific actions",
                        "answer": ["Instructing"],
                        "id": 219
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Expecting response from the computer",
                        "answer": ["Conversing"],
                        "id": 220
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Cotrolling software applications",
                        "answer": ["Manipulating"],
                        "id": 221
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Navigating or discovering the system or application.",
                        "answer": ["Exploring"],
                        "id": 222
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Responding of a computer to the user and vice versa.",
                        "answer": ["Responding"],
                        "id": 223
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Responding"], ["Exploring"], ["Manipulating"], ["Conversing"], ["Instructing"]],
                    "question": "Types of interactions",
                    "id": 217
                }
            },

            "Models_of_interaction": {
                "answers": ["Normans Seven Stages of Action", "GOMS model", "Model Human Processor (MHP)"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "This model is widely used in the field of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) and user experience (UX) design to understand how users interact with systems and how design can influence the user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Normans Seven Stages of Action", "Norman Seven Stages", "Norman's Seven Stage"],
                        "id": 225
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "This model emphasizes that the user experience goes beyond usability and functionality, considering the emotional and hedonic aspects of user interactions.",
                        "answer": ["Hassenzahl UX Model"],
                        "id": 226
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Norman's Seven Stages of action", "Norman Seven Stages", "Norman's Seven Stage"], ["GOMS model", "GOMS"], ["Model Human Processor", "MHP", "Model Human Processor (MHP)"], ["Hassenzahl UX Model", "Hassenzahl UX Models"]],
                    "question": "Models of interactions",
                    "id": 224
                }
            },

            "Frameworks_of_Interaction": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [

                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Five Dimesions of Interaction Design", "Five Dimesions of Interaction Designs", "Five Dimesions of Interactions Design", "Five Dimesion of Interaction Design"], ["UX Design pyramid", "UX Design pyramids", "UX Designs pyramid"], ["5E Experience Design Model", "5E Experience Design Models", "5E Experience Designs Model"], ["Donal Norman's coceptual of the system image", "Donal Norman's coceptual of the system images"]],
                    "question": "Frameworks of Intrerations",
                    "id": 227
                }
            },

            "5E_Experience": {
                "answers": ["Entry", "Engagement", "Exit", "Extension", "Excitement"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the application is now deployed",
                        "answer": ["Entry"],
                        "id": 229
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the team will organizing events and other strategies to keep users using the app",
                        "answer": ["Engagement", "Engagements"],
                        "id": 230
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "This the fourth phase in 5E Experience Design Model",
                        "answer": ["Exit"],
                        "id": 231
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the application has a extra features to keep the user using their app. ex. notifications, event, daily rewards.",
                        "answer": ["Extension", "Extension"],
                        "id": 232
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the team is makig a promotional events like advertisement before deploying the app",
                        "answer": ["Excitement", "Excitements"],
                        "id": 233
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Entry"], ["Engagement","Engagements"], ["Exit"], ["Extension", "Extensions"], ["Excitement", "Excitements"]],
                    "question": "Steps in 5E Experience Design Model",
                    "id": 228
                }
            },

            "HCI_Interaction": {
                "answers": ["Ergonomics", "Framework", "Model"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "__________, also known as human factors engineering, aims to create systems and environments that are comfortable, efficient, safe, and conducive to human well-being during computer use.",
                        "answer": ["Ergonomics", "Ergonomic"],
                        "id": 233
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Help to describe and explain various facets of human-computer interaction.",
                        "answer": ["Model", "Models"],
                        "id": 234
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "In HCI provides a structured approach, set of principles, or guidelines for designing, evaluating, or analyzing aspects of human-computer interaction.",
                        "answer": ["Framework", "Frameworks"],
                        "id": 235
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            },

            "Five_Dimensions_of_Interaction": {
                "answers": ["Word", "Visual Representation", "Physical objects or white space", "Time", "Behavior"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "What does 1D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                        "answer": ["Word", "Words"],
                        "id": 237
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "What does 2D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                        "answer": ["Visual Representation", "Visuals Representations", "Visuals Representation", "Visual Representations"],
                        "id": 238
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "What does 3D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                        "answer": ["Physical objects or white space", "Physical Objects", "Physical Object", "White space", "White Spaces"],
                        "id": 239
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "What does 4D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                        "answer":["Time"],
                        "id": 240
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "What does 5D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                        "answer": ["Behavior", "Behaviors"],
                        "id": 241
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Word", "Words"], ["Visual Representation", "Visuals Representations", "Visuals Representation", "Visual Representations"], ["Physical objects or white space", "Physical Objects", "Physical Object", "White space", "White Spaces"], ["Time"], ["Behavior", "Behaviors"]],
                    "question": "Ds in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                    "id": 236
                }
            },

            "UX_design_pyramid": {
                "answers": ["Significant", "Enjoyable", "Convenient", "Usable", "Reliable", "Functional"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, the application is working.",
                        "answer": ["functional", "functionals"],
                        "id": 243
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are using the app to accomplish a task.",
                        "answer": ["Usable"],
                        "id": 244
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are now using the app more than you need.",
                        "answer": ["Convenient", "Convenients"],
                        "id": 245
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are now relying on this app.",
                        "answer": ["Enjoyable"],
                        "id": 246
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you can't live without this app.",
                        "answer": ["Significant", "Significants"],
                        "id": 247
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Significant", "Significants"], ["Enjoyable"], ["Convenient", "Convenients"], ["Usable"], ["Reliable"], ["functional", "functionals"]],
                    "question": "UX design pyramid levels",
                    "id": 242
                }
            },

            "Design_Principles_for_Interaction": {
                "answers": ["Visibility", "Feedback", "Constraints", "Consistency", "Mapping", "Affordance"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "It is the basic principle that the more visible an element is, the more likely user will know about them and how to use them.",
                        "answer": ["Visibility", "Visibilities"],
                        "id": 249
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "It is the principle of making it clear to the user what action has been taken and what has been accomplished.",
                        "answer": ["Feedback", "Feedbacks"],
                        "id": 250
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Is a about limiting the range of iteraction possibilities for the user to simplify the interface and guide the user to appropriate next action.",
                        "answer": ["Constraints", "Constraint"],
                        "id": 251
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to having similar operations and similar elements for achieving similar tasks.",
                        "answer": ["Consistency", "Consistencies"],
                        "id": 252
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Is about having a clear realationship between controls and the effect they have on the world.",
                        "answer": ["Mapping"],
                        "id": 253
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the attribute of the objects that allows people to know how to use it",
                        "answer": ["Affordance"],
                        "id": 254
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Visibility", "Visibilities"], ["Feedback", "Feedbacks"], ["Constraints", "Constraint"], ["Consistency", "Consistencies"], ["Mapping"], ["Affordance"]],
                    "question": "Design Principles for Interaction",
                    "id": 248
                }
            }
        },

        "Chapter_3": {
            "The_User_Experience": {
                "answers": ["User Experience (UX)", "User Interface (UI)", "Human-Computer Interaction"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The totality of effects felt by the user as a result of interacftion.",
                        "answer": ["The user experience","User experience","UX","The user experiences","User experiences","The users experiences","users experiences","users experience", "User Experience (UX)", "UX", "User Experience(UX)", "(UX)"],
                        "id": 83
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is the overall experience that a user has when interacting with a product or service.",
                        "answer": ["User Experience (UX)","User Experience(UX)","User Experience","UX","User Experiences","Users Experience","Users Experiences"],
                        "id": 84
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is the visual and interactive elements of a product or service.",
                        "answer": ["User Interface (UI)","User Interface(UI)","User Interface","UI","Users Interface"],
                        "id": 85
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is a field of study that focuses on the design and use of computer technology, specifically the interaction between humans and computers",
                        "answer": ["Human-Computer Interaction","Human Computer Interaction","HCI"],
                        "id": 86
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It refers to the visual elements that allow users to interact with a product.",
                        "answer": ["User Interface (UI)","User Interface(UI)","User Interface","UI","Users Interface"],
                        "id": 87
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It foucuses on the look of the product. Typography, colors, images and more.",
                        "answer": ["User Interface (UI)","User Interface(UI)","User Interface","UI","Users Interface"],
                        "id": 88
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The goal is to make the product more usable, aesthetically appealing, and optimized for different screen sizes.",
                        "answer": ["User Interface (UI)","User Interface(UI)","User Interface","UI","Users Interface"],
                        "id": 89
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It's about feelings and emotions users experience when interacting with a product.",
                        "answer": ["User Experience (UX)","User Experience(UX)","User Experience","UX","User Experiences","Users Experience","Users Experiences"],
                        "id": 90
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            },

            "The_User_Experience_Design": {
                "answers": ["User Interface Design", "User Experience Design", "Surface", "Strategy", "Scope", "Structure", "Skeleton"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "The process of creating products and experience that help users get done what theyve come to do. Satisfying users needs.",
                        "answer": ["User Experience Design","User Experience Designs","User Experiences Designs","Users Experiences Designs","Users Experiences Design","UXD"],
                        "id": 91
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The process of designing the visual and interactive elements of a product or service.",
                        "answer": ["User Interface Design","User Interface Designs","User Interfaces Designs","Users Interfaces Designs","Users Interface Designs","UI Design","UID"],
                        "id": 92
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Who and why are you designing for? (Users needs and Product Objectives)",
                        "answer": ["Strategy", "Strategies"],
                        "id": 93
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "What are you designing, what the solutions does? (Features and COntent Requirements)",
                        "answer": ["Scope", "Scopes"],
                        "id": 94
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "How the product or solution works, create a blueprint on how the user interact with it? (Interaction Design and information Architecture)",
                        "answer": ["Structure", "Structures"],
                        "id": 95
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "First interface of the solution, or the tangible elements of the ux? (Information, interface and Navigation Design)",
                        "answer": ["Skeleton"],
                        "id": 96
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The most visible element. The users see and interact with? (Visual design)",
                        "answer": ["Surface", "Surfaces"],
                        "id": 97
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            },

            "Importance_of_User_Experience_Design": {
                "answers": ["Business Success", "Cost Reduction", "Safety and Convenience", "Overall User Satisfaction", "User-centric Approach"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the positive impact that a well-designed user experience can have on a company's profitability, growth, and competitiveness.",
                        "answer": ["Business Success"],
                        "id": 98
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The use of prototype to reduce resources.",
                        "answer": ["Cost Reduction", "Cost Reductions", "Costs Reduction", "Costs Reductions"],
                        "id": 99
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Designing interfaces and interactions that prioritize user safety, security, and ease of use.",
                        "answer": ["Safety and Convenience", "Safeties and Convenience"],
                        "id": 100
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Refers to how well a product or system meets users' needs, expectations, and preferences, resulting in a positive user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Overall User Satisfaction","Overall User Satisfactions","Overall Users Satisfactions"],
                        "id": 101
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Involves placing the needs and preferences of users at the forefront of the design and development process",
                        "answer": ["User-centric Approach","User centric Approach","Users centric Approach","User centric Approaches"],
                        "id": 102
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Business Success"], ["Cost Reduction", "Cost Reductions", "Costs Reduction", "Costs Reductions"], ["Safety and Convenience"], ["Overall User Satisfaction", "Overall User's Satisfactions"],["User-centric Approach", "User centric Approach", "User centric Approaches"]],
                    "question": "Importance of User Experience Design",
                    "id": 103
                }
            },

            "Components_of_User_Experience": {
                "answers": ["Usability", "Usefulness", "Emotional Impact", "Meaningfulness"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Productivity, efficiency, ease of use, learnability.",
                        "answer": ["Usability", "Usabilities"],
                        "id": 104
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Ability to use system or product to accomplish goals of work.",
                        "answer": ["Usefulness"],
                        "id": 105
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Affective component of user experience and user feelings, user satisfaction.",
                        "answer": ["Emotional Impact", "Emotional Impacts", "Emotional Impact"],
                        "id": 106
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Long-term personal relationship with product.",
                        "answer": ["Meaningfulness"],
                        "id": 107
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Usability"], ["Usefulness"], ["Emotional Impact", "Emotional Impacts"], ["Meaningfulness"]],
                    "question": "Components of User Experience",
                    "id": 108
                }
            },

            "Misconceptions_about_User_Experience": {
                "answers": [],
                "questions": [],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["UX is not about dummy proofing or user-friendlyness.", "UX is not about dummy proofing or user-friendlyness", "UX is not about dummy proofing or user friendlyness.", "UX is not about dummy proofing or user friendlyness"], 
                                ["UX is not just dressing things up in pretty skin.", "UX is not just dressing things up in pretty skin", "UX is not just dressing things up in pretty skins", "UX is not just dressing things up in pretty skins."], 
                                ["UX is not just a diagnostic view.", "UX is not just a diagnostic view", "UX is not just a diagnostic views", "UX is not just a diagnostic views.", "UX is not just a diagnostics views", "UX is not just a diagnostics views.", "UX is not just a diagnostics view."]],
                    "question": "Misconceptions about User Experience",
                    "id": 109
                }
            },

            "Kind_of_Interaction_and_User_Experience": {
                "answers": ["Activity-based Interaction", "Localized Interaction", "System spanning"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Type of interaction that has more interactions. Like gcash in shopee",
                        "answer": ["System spanning"],
                        "id": 110
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "This interaction is one purpose only or limited action",
                        "answer": ["Localized Interaction", "Localized", "Localized Interactions", "Localize Interaction", "Localize Interactions"],
                        "id": 111
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Perform many task in in one activity",
                        "answer": ["Activity-based Interaction", "Activity based Interaction", "Activity-based Interactions", "Activity based Interactions"],
                        "id": 112
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Activity-based Interaction", "Activity based Interaction", "Activity-based Interactions", "Activity based Interactions"], 
                    ["Localized Interaction", "Localized Interactions", "Localize Interactions", "Localize Interaction"], ["System spanning", "Systems spanning"]],
                    "question": "Kinds of Interaction and User Experience",
                    "id": 113
                }
            },

            "The_Need_for_a_process": {
                "answers": ["Shared Conception", "Scaffolding for Learning", "Reliability and Consistency", "Systematic Approach", "Guiding Structure"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "A step-by-step approach followed to create user-centered experience and prototypes, from unnderstanding user needs to evaluating the final design.",
                        "answer": ["Process"],
                        "id": 114
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "A well-defined process provides a clear path for designing and evaluating user interfaces, ensuring that all relevant aspects are considered.",
                        "answer": ["Guiding Structure", "Guiding Structures"],
                        "id": 115
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "A process helps in systematically identifying user needs, conducting research, prototyping, testing, and iterating, leading to more effective HCI solutions.",
                        "answer": ["Systematic Approach", "Systematic Approaches", "Systematics Approach"],
                        "id": 116
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": " Following a consistent process promotes reliability in design outcomes, making it easier to replicate successful designs and avoid errors.",
                        "answer": ["Reliability and Consistency", "Reliabilities and Consistencies", "Reliabilities and Consistency", "Reliability and Consistencies"],
                        "id": 117
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "A process can serve as a framework for both newcomers and experienced professionals, helping them understand and teach HCI principles and methods.",
                        "answer": ["Scaffolding for Learning", "Scaffoldings for Learnings", "Scaffolding for Learnings", "Scaffoldings for Learnings"],
                        "id": 118
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "Having a standardized process fosters a common understanding among team members, facilitating collaboration and communication in HCI projects.",
                        "answer": ["Shared Conception", "Shared Conceptions"],
                        "id": 119
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Shared Conception", "Shared Conceptions"], ["Scaffolding for Learning", "Scaffolding for Learnings", "Scaffolding in Learning"], ["Reliability and Consistency", "Reliabilities and Consistency"], ["Systematic Approach"], ["Guiding Structure", "Guiding Structures"]],
                    "question": "Benefits of Having a Process",
                    "id": 120
                }
            },

            "The_Basic_Process_Components_for_UX": {
                "answers": ["UX Design Lifecycle", "UX Design Lifecycle Process","UX Lifecycle Methods","UX Lifecycle Model","UX Lifecycle Activities","UX Lifecycle Techniques","UX Lifecycle Subactivities"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "It is cycle that emcompasses the process of designing a user experience, starting from ideation to deployment and beyond.",
                        "answer": ["UX Design Lifecycle", "UX Design Lifecycles"],
                        "id": 122
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is a depiction of how the activities of the lifecycle are organized and arrange in chronological.",
                        "answer": ["UX Design Lifecycle Process", "UX Design Lifecycles Process"],
                        "id": 123
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is a structured framework that guides the process of designing a user experience.",
                        "answer": ["UX Lifecycle Model", "UX Lifecycle Models", "UX Lifecycles Models"],
                        "id": 124
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "These are the essential tasks and steps that are performed during the process of creating a user experience.",
                        "answer": ["UX Lifecycle Activities", "UX Lifecycles Activities"],
                        "id": 125
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "These are the different approaches used to carry out the main activities or subactivities in the user experience design process.",
                        "answer": ["UX Lifecycle Methods", "UX Lifecycle Method", "UX Lifecycles Methods"],
                        "id": 126
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "These are specific, detailed practices used to perform individual steps within the activities, subactivities, or methods of the user experience design process.",
                        "answer": ["UX Lifecycle Techniques", "UX Lifecycle Technique", "UX Lifecycles Techniques"],
                        "id": 127
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Specific tasks and actions performed within each main activity if the user experience design process.",
                        "answer": ["UX Lifecycle Subactivities", "UX Lifecycles Subactivities", "UX Lifecycle Sub-activities"],
                        "id": 121
                    }

                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["UX Design Lifecycle"], ["UX Design Lifecycle Process"],["UX Lifecycle Methods", "UX Lifecycle Method"],["UX Lifecycle Model", "UX Lifecycle Model"],["UX Lifecycle Activities"],["UX Lifecycle Techniques", "UX Lifecycle Technique"],["UX Lifecycle Subactivities"]],
                    "question": "The Basic Process Components for UX",
                    "id": 128
                }
            },

            "UX_Design_Techniques_as_Life_Skills": {
                "answers": ["Iteration", "Critical Thinking", "Prototyping and Envisioning", "Reasoning and Deduction", "Framing and Reframing", "Sketching and Drawing", "Observation", "Abstraction", "Note Taking", "Data Organization", "Modeling", "Storytelling", "Immersion", "Brainstorming"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Involves keenly and objectively watching people, events, or situations to gather information and insights.",
                        "answer": ["Observation", "Observations"], 
                        "id": 129
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is the process of simplifying complex information or concepts into more manageable and understandable forms.",
                        "answer": ["Abstraction", "Abstractions"],
                        "id": 130
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Involves recording important information, ideas, or observations for future reference or organization.",
                        "answer": ["Note Taking", "Notes Taking"],
                        "id": 131
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is the skill of structuring and categorizing information logically and efficiently.",
                        "answer": ["Data Organization", "Data Organizations"],
                        "id": 132
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "entails creating representations or visualizations of objects, systems, or processes to understand them better.",
                        "answer": ["Modeling"],
                        "id": 133
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "is the art of conveying information, ideas, or experiences through narratives that engage and captivate an audience.",
                        "answer": ["Storytelling"],
                        "id": 134
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "involves fully engaging in an experience or environment to gain a deep understanding of it.",
                        "answer": ["Immersion" ,"Immersions"],
                        "id": 135
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "is a creative technique for generating a wide range of ideas and solutions within a group.",
                        "answer": ["Brainstorming"],
                        "id": 136
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "involve visually representing ideas, concepts, or designs through hand-drawn images.",
                        "answer": ["Sketching and Drawing"],
                        "id": 137
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "is the way in which a problem or situation is presented, and involves looking at it from different perspectives.",
                        "answer": ["Framing and Reframing"],
                        "id": 138
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "is the ability to form logical conclusions, and involves drawing specific conclusions from general information.",
                        "answer": ["Reasoning and Deduction", "Reasoning and Deductions"],
                        "id": 139
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "is the creation of preliminary models or representations of a design or idea, and involves imagining future scenarios.",
                        "answer": ["Prototyping and Envisioning"],
                        "id": 140
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "involves analyzing and evaluating information or arguments.",
                        "answer": ["Critical Thinking"],
                        "id": 141
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Refers to the process of refining and improving a design through multiple cycles or rounds of evaluation, feedback, and revision.",
                        "answer": ["Iteration", "Iterations"],
                        "id": 142
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Iteration", "Iterations"], ["Critical Thinking"], ["Prototyping and Envisioning"], ["Reasoning and Deduction", "Reasoning and Deductions"], ["Framing and Reframing"], ["Sketching and Drawing"],
                                ["Observation", "Observations"], ["Abstraction", "Abstractions"], ["Note Taking", "Notes Taking"], ["Data Organization", "Data Organizations"],["Modeling"], ["Storytelling"], ["Immersion" ,"Immersions"], ["Brainstorming"]],
                    "question": "UX Design Techniques as Life Skills",
                    "id": 143
                }
            },

            "Fundamental_UX_Lifecycle_Activities": {
                "answers": ["Report Results", "Propose Redisign Solution", "Analyze Evaluation Data", "Collect Evaluation Data", "Build Physical Prototypes","Develop Click-Through Wireframe Prototypes","Build Wireframes and Wireflows","Create Paper Prototype","Intermediate Design","Design Production","Conceptual Design","Generative Design","Requirements Extraction","Data modeling","Data Analysis","Data Elicitation","Evalute UX","Prototype Candidates","Design Solution","Understand Needs"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "This activity involves gaining insights into users, their work practices, usage patterns, and the subject-matter domain to understand their needs and requirements for the design.",
                        "answer": ["Understand Needs", "Understand Need", "Understand Need"],
                        "id": 144
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "In this activity, designer create designs as solutions to address the identified user needs and challenges.",
                        "answer": ["Design Solution", "Designs Solutions", "Design Solutions"], 
                        "id": 145
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Designers build prototypes of promising design solutions to visualize and test their effectiveness.",
                        "answer": ["Prototype Candidates", "Prototypes Candidates", "Prototype Candidate"], 
                        "id": 146
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This activity involves verifying and refining the designs based on user feedback and insight to ensure a positive user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Evalute UX", "Evalutes UX", "Evalute User Experience"], 
                        "id": 147
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This involves interviewing and observing users while they work to gather data about their practices, preference, and needs.",
                        "answer": ["Data Elicitation", "Data Elicitations"], 
                        "id": 148
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The collected usage research data is distilled and organized for better comprehension.",
                        "answer": ["Data Analysis"], 
                        "id": 149
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Representation are created to capture user characteristics, information, flow, tasks, and work environments. These model aid collaboration, sharing, archival, rehearsal, and immension.",
                        "answer": ["Data modeling"],
                        "id": 150
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This subacitivity invloves codifying the needs and requirements identified during the reseach process.",
                        "answer": ["Requirements Extraction", "Requirements Extractions", "Requirement Extraction"],
                        "id": 151
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "In This sub-activity, designers engage in ideation and sketching to create various design ideas.",
                        "answer": ["Generative Design", "Generative Designs"],
                        "id": 152
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This sub-activity involves creating mental models, system models, and storyboards to flesh out the design concepts.",
                        "answer": ["Conceptual Design", "Conceptual Designs"],
                        "id": 153
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This sub-activity focuses on specifying detailed plans for implementing the selected design.",
                        "answer": ["Design Production", "Design Productions", "Designs Production", "Designs Productions"],
                        "id": 154
                    },
        
                    {
                        "question": "In this place, desingers develop ecological, interaction, and emotional design plans for the most promising candidates.",
                        "answer": ["Intermediate Design", "Intermediate Designs"],
                        "id": 155
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "DEsigners develop hand-drawn or printed paper prototypes to explore and visualize design concepts in low fidelity.",
                        "answer": ["Create Paper Prototype", "Create Paper Prototypes"],
                        "id": 156
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Designers create basic visual representations of the user interface and interaction flow.",
                        "answer": ["Build Wireframes and Wireflows", "Build Wireframe and Wireflow", "Build Wireframes and Wireflow", "Build Wireframe and Wireflows", "Builds Wireframes and Wireflows", "Builds Wireframe and Wireflow"],
                        "id": 157
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Desingers create interactive prototypes that allow users to navigate through the design with clickable elements, providing a more dynamic representation of the user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Develop Click-Through Wireframe Prototypes", "Develop Click Through Wireframe Prototypes", "Develop Click Through Wireframe Prototype"],
                        "id": 158
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "For physical products or tangible interactions, designers create physical prototyes to test and evaluate the designs functionality and usability.",
                        "answer": ["Build Physical Prototypes", "Build Physical Prototype"],
                        "id": 159
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Desingers use various methods, such as user testing, surveys, or analysis, to gather data on how users interact with the design. This data provides valuable insights into user behavior and preferences.",
                        "answer": ["Collect Evaluation Data", "Collects Evaluations Data", "Collects Evaluation Data", "Collect Evaluations Data"],
                        "id": 160
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The collected daya is analyzed to identify patterns, official incidents, and root causes. This analysis helps designers understand the strengths and weakness of the design.",
                        "answer": ["Analyze Evaluation Data", "Analyze Evaluations Data"],
                        "id": 161
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Based on the evaluation results, designers propose changes and improvements to address identified issues and enhance the user experience.",
                        "answer": ["Propose Redisign Solution", "Propose Redisign Solutions"],
                        "id": 162
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The evaluation findings and proposed redesign solution solution are documented and communicated to stakeholders and the design team. This ensures everyone knows the evaluation outcomes and the design team. This ensures everyone knows the evaluation outcomes and the next steps for refining the design.",
                        "answer": ["Report Results", "Report Result"],
                        "id": 163
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Report Results", "Report Result"], ["Propose Redisign Solution", "Propose Redisign Solutions"], ["Analyze Evaluation Data", "Analyze Evaluations Data"],
                                ["Collect Evaluation Data", "Collects Evaluations Data", "Collects Evaluation Data", "Collect Evaluations Data"], ["Build Physical Prototypes", "Build Physical Prototype"],
                                ["Build Wireframes and Wireflows", "Build Wireframe and Wireflow", "Build Wireframes and Wireflow", "Build Wireframe and Wireflows", "Builds Wireframes and Wireflows", "Builds Wireframe and Wireflow"],
                                ["Create Paper Prototype", "Create Paper Prototypes"], ["Intermediate Design", "Intermediate Designs"], ["Design Production", "Design Productions", "Designs Production", "Designs Productions"],
                                ["Conceptual Design", "Conceptual Designs"], ["Generative Design", "Generative Designs"], ["Requirements Extraction", "Requirements Extractions", "Requirement Extraction"], 
                                ["Data Analysis"], ["Data modeling"],  ["Data Elicitation", "Data Elicitations"], ["Evalute UX", "Evalutes UX", "Evalute User Experience"],  ["Prototype Candidates", "Prototypes Candidates", "Prototype Candidate"], 
                                ["Design Solution", "Designs Solutions", "Design Solutions"], ["Understand Needs", "Understand Need", "Understand Need"]],
                    "question": "Fundamentals UX Lifecycle Activities",
                    "id": 164
                }
            }
        }
    },

    "DSA": {
        "Chapter_1": {
            "Fundamentals_Properties": {
                "answers": ["Finiteness", "Definiteness", "Input", "Output", "Effectiveness"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "An algorithm must terminate after a finite number of steps.",
                        "answer": ["Finiteness","Finite"],
                        "id": 37
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Algorithm is precisely defined.",
                        "answer": ["Definiteness"],
                        "id": 38
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Domain of the algorithm which could be zero or more quantities.",
                        "answer": ["Input","Inputs"],
                        "id": 39
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Set one or more resulting quantities. Also called the range of the algorithm.",
                        "answer": ["Output","Outputs"],
                        "id": 40
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Ensured if all the operations in the algorithm are sufficiently basic that they can, in principle, be done exactly and in finite time by a person using paper and pen.",
                        "answer": ["Effectiveness"],
                        "id": 41
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Finiteness"], ["Definiteness"], ["Input", "Inputs"], ["Output", "Outputs"], ["Effectiveness"]],
                    "question": "Enumerate the fundamentals properties of algorithms.",
                    "id": 42
                }
            },

            "Mathematical_functions": {
                "answers": ["Floor", "Ceiling", "Modulo"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Greatest integer less than or equal to x (x is any real  number).",
                        "answer": ["Floor"],
                        "id": 43
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Smallest integer greater than or equal to x ",
                        "answer": ["Ceiling"],
                        "id": 44
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Given any two real numbers x and y.",
                        "answer": ["Modulo"],
                        "id": 45
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [["Floor"], ["Cieling"], ["Modulo"]],
                    "question": "Mathematical functions",
                    "id": 46
                }
            },

            "Measuring_algorithm_efficiency": {
                "answers": ["Time complexity", "Execution time", "Space complexity", "The Empirical Method", "The Theoretical Method", "Process"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "Quantifies the amount of time taken by an algorithm to run as a function of the length of the input.",
                        "answer": ["Time complexity","Time complexity(Time Efficiency)","Time complexity (Time Efficiency)","Time Efficiency","Time complexities"],
                        "id": 47
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Amount of time spent in executing instructions of a given akgorithm. Notation: T(n). Several factors: input size, instruction type, machine speed, quality of source of the algorithm implementation, quality of the machine code generated from the source code by the computer.",
                        "answer": ["Execution time","Execution","Executing time"],
                        "id": 48
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Quantifies the amount of space or memory taken by an algorithm to run as a function of the lenght of the input.",
                        "answer": ["Space complexity","Space complexity(Space Utilization)","Space complexity(Space Utilizations)","Space complexity (Space Utilization)","Space complexity (Space Utilizations)","Space Utilization","Space Utilizations","Spaxe complexities"],
                        "id": 49
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "A method of analyzing an algorithm by determining: the number of times eacch program line runs, time required to execute each line, no. of times each procedures were called, total space alocated to run the program, etc.",
                        "answer": ["The Empirical Method","The Empirical Methods","Empirical Method","Empirical Methods","Empirical"],
                        "id": 50
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "The analysis solely on the way algorithms solve problems.",
                        "answer": ["The Theoretical Method","The Theoretical Methods","Theoretical Method","Theoretical Methods","Theoretical"],
                        "id": 51
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "What the designer can control.",
                        "answer": ["Process","Processes"],
                        "id": 52
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            }
        },

        "Chapter_2": {
            "Basic_Array_Concepts": {
                "answers": ["Array", "ArrayList", "List", "Linear list", "Generalized list", "Linked list", "Node", "Info", "Link", "Singly Linked List", "Head", "NULL", "Doubly Linked List", "Next link", "Prev link"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "It is a numbered collection of variables all of the same type.",
                        "answer": ["Array"],
                        "id": 53
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It provides us with dynamic arrays in java. It is similar to vector in C++.",
                        "answer": ["ArrayList"],
                        "id": 54
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is a data structure that is based on sequences of items.",
                        "answer": ["List"],
                        "id": 55
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Contains atom elements only, and are sequentially ordered.",
                        "answer": ["Linear list"],
                        "id": 56
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Could contain both list and atom elements.",
                        "answer": ["Generalized list","Generalize","Generalized","Generalize list"],
                        "id": 57
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Is a collection of nodes that together form a linear ordering. A linear data structure in which the elements are not stored at contiguous memory locations.",
                        "answer": ["Linked list"],
                        "id": 58
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "It is a collection of two sub-elements or parts.",
                        "answer": ["Node","Nodes"],
                        "id": 59
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "(Link list)Store relevant information.",
                        "answer": ["Info",".info","info()",".info()"],
                        "id": 60
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Store the address of the next node.",
                        "answer": ["Link","Next","Link / Next","Link/Next",".next",".next()"],
                        "id": 61
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "A linked list is formed when many such nodes are linked together to form a chain.",
                        "answer": ["Singly Linked List","Singly"],
                        "id": 62
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "The first node in the linked list is called.",
                        "answer": ["Head"],
                        "id": 63
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Last node in the linked list is pointed to.",
                        "answer": ["NULL"],
                        "id": 64
                    },

                    {
                        "question": "Type of linked list that allows us to go in both directions.",
                        "answer": ["Doubly Linked List","Doubly"],
                        "id": 65
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Points the next node in the list.",
                        "answer": ["Next link","next"],
                        "id": 66
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Points the previous node in the list.",
                        "answer": ["Prev link","prev"],
                        "id": 67
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            },

            "ArrayList": {
                "answers": ["add(int index, Object element)", "add(Object)", "clear()", "isEmpty()", "remove(int index)", "size()", "get(int index)"],
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "This method is used to appened specific element at a specific position index in a list.",
                        "answer": ["add(int index, Object element)",".add(index, element)",".add(i, object)",".add(int, object)","add(int, object)","add(int, element)"],
                        "id": 68
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This method is used to appened specific element to the end of a list.",
                        "answer": ["add(Object)",".add(Object)",".add(Element)","add(Element)"],
                        "id": 69
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "This method is used to remove all the elements from any list.",
                        "answer": ["clear()",".clear()",".clear"],
                        "id": 70
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Returns true if the list has no elements.",
                        "answer": ["isEmpty()","isEmpty?()",".isEmpty?()",".isEmpty()"],
                        "id": 71
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Remove elements at the specific position in the list.",
                        "answer": ["remove(int index)","remove(int)",".remove(int)",".remove(index)","remove?(int index)","remove?(int)","remove?(index)"],
                        "id": 72
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Returns the number of elements in the list.",
                        "answer": ["size()",".size()","size?()",".size?()"],
                        "id": 73
                    },
                    
                    {
                        "question": "Returns the element at the specific position in the list.",
                        "answer": ["get(int index)",".get(int index)",".get(int)",".get(index)","get(int)","get(index)"],
                        "id": 74
                    }
                ],

                "enumeration": {
                    "answers": [],
                    "question": "",
                    "id": 99999
                }
            }
        }
    },

    "OOP": {

    },

    "PE": {

    },

    "PUR_COM": {

    }
}